sick of their culture. I'm mostly sick
about how my life is not going anywhere
and everybody's life passed me by
and nothing ever gets done.
Nothing ever gets done. These people
never change. I waste my whole life
away. I'm sick of it.
I'm sick of my life going nowhere while
I have to stare these people down the
neck. I'm sick of it.
I'm really sick of it.
I deserve to have success, have an ex
success one time in my life. I work
[__] hard for this.
But what's wrong with my life? Why is it
that no one can recognize what I've
given to the world? I'm sick of it. I'm
sick of it. I'm sick of being treated
like [__]
Sick of America. Sick of America. Sick
of culture.
sick of
sick.
I wasted my life away doing these things
and it makes me a little bit angry.
I I don't get anything for it and I want
something for it.
I work hard.
I suffer for this [__] [__] world
more than enough. more too much
and no one ever says thank you. No one
ever grows with me. No one ever cares
about me.
And so
I don't think those people that joined
my Discord cares about me either. They
don't never type me.
They're not there to grow. Like it's
it's the same. I'm like, it just make me
sick. These stupid fat Americans are
stuck, ugly faces. They don't change
nothing. They never say sorry,
right? They never apologize. They never
say anything. They never figure out that
they should apologize for all the sins
that they made and all the pain that
they gave me. What are they going to do
to repair what they have broken?
Why do they never figure out that I'm
actually angry and it's their fault?
Well, it makes me angry because my life
has been stalled due to this their
stupid culture and their stupid c and
they couldn't just let me go. They
couldn't just leave me alone,
right? They couldn't just let me live a
life. They couldn't just leave me alone
and they couldn't just grow and they
couldn't just be better people and they
couldn't say sorry. They couldn't do any
of these things. Not a single one of
these things. And my life has been
stalled because of these [__]
And they dare to come into my life over
and over and over and over and over over
again
who started this. These same people that
keep walking into my life and never
apologizing.
Right. The same people that were here 10
years ago
like Sammy is stupid [__] and all these
other [__] ugly people. Dude,
it just makes me sick. Everybody that
sits in that stupid discord with that
stupid dog, right? They should be
dissolved.
They should be forced or they should go
to jail cuz I'm sick of it.
I'm sick of them actually [__]
hanging out together. I'm sick of them
actually talking together.
I'm sick of them existing.
That's how sick I am. And I know exactly
who they are. I know them all very well.
And I don't want to be near them. Not
only do I not want to be near them, I do
not want them to be friends with one
another. I don't want them to have any
kind of life. I want them to go to jail
or they can line up in a [__] line
and apologize every day for the rest of
their sorry life.
But they don't do that. They don't even
say sorry once. They don't even do
anything to repair what was broken.
So I'm pissed off.
Right? Because why wouldn't I be?
Because at the end of the day, a lot of
people owe me a lot of things and I want
my money.
I want my retirement. I'm retired.
Right? I'm retired. What does that tell
people? I was retired in this country.
What do they think? Why do they think I
was retired? I told it very clear. I'm
retired because people are stalking me
online, right? So, when will somebody
apologize for that?
Cuz I'm still here waiting.
I'm still here.
Does that make any sense to you?
I should not have to take this [__] I
should not have to be put for this. I
have ADHD. I have a mental handicap. Be
put for that. Why do Why does it Why is
it right for people to bully handicap
people online? Why is that right? But
I'm just sitting there and have that
[__] life and I don't have a [__]
life. Why is that okay? Why is that okay
that they have a [__] life and I
don't have a [__] life? Why is that
okay?
Why are psychopaths and psychopaths
getting away with getting having a nice
life when I don't have any life at all?
Huh? Can you explain that to me?
No, you can't
again because and how many times have
you been here? They're not talking about
Discord, sir. They're not growing.
They're not doing the thing. How many
times have I been at a point where I
just say, "No, look, they gave them days
to do anything. They haven't done
anything. I'm going to kick them out
again. They're going to ask, "Hey, can
we get into the server again?" They're
going to do and we're in the cycle and I
don't want to It's I don't want to be
part of their [__] lives.
Do they not understand? They not They
need to do some things.
Do they not understand?
Right. They don't understand. No one
understands
that it's not okay. And I'm not okay.
And people are not okay. And I hate
America. And I hate Americans. And they
should be repenting their sins, but they
don't. And they keep sinking. And I'm so
sick of the I'm sick of America. Stupid
fat ass [__] piss blow [__] ass
country. Right. I'm the greatest person
in the world. I'm the greatest god in
the world. I have 100,000 hours. Make me
famous, you [__] fat [__]
How about that?
Make that go viral. You [__] fat
Americans.
You hear that? I am peak culture.
I am the ruler of the [__] universe.
And you are my passions. You are my
slaves.
Do you understand that, America? You are
my [__] property. Every inch of your
[__] dust of your country is mine.
I'm the king of gangs. I own heaven and
I own every clot of your mind. I own
your [__] existence. Do you
understand me, America? Do you
understand me, America?
Do you understand? You have taken from
me. You have taken from my life. You are
taken from goodness and truth. You have
taken from heaven. You have taken from
God.
You have taken from the future. You have
taken from the afterlife.
You have taken what you should not take.
And you have violated boundaries over
and over and over again cuz you're human
traffickers and you're scammers
and you are evil and you would never
change and you would never say sorry.
You are a nation full of demons. You do
not believe in God. You believe in
ultimate doom. You believe in death. You
believe in coercion. You believe in
threats. You believe in violence. You
believe in dehumanization.
You believe in demology.
You believe in the past. You believe in
death. You believe in destruction.
[__] you.
[__] you. sincerely from peak culture
and base reality. You're number two. In
fact, you're number
of the [__] You don't have freedom. You
have incarceration.
You don't have nothing. You have
slavery.
You don't even have a culture. You don't
even have a foundation. You don't have a
future.
Listen to me. You don't have a future.
You entangle your fates and your
destinies with me. And then you walked
away as if nothing's going to happen.
But does it sound like um does it sound
like nothing's going to happen? Huh? I
hope a bomb drops on your [__]
houses. And I hope your existence is
finished. And I hope you have nothing
left when all is said and done.
And I hope you suffer. I hope you suffer
for a long time.
[__] Americans.
[__] their culture. [__] their country.
[__] their people.
Everything that they have.
People think it's a joke storing
anything. They don't care about anything
matter if you're mentally handicapped or
if you you can't feel your emotions,
right? They don't care about it. They
can't even admit that they're sociopaths
or psychopaths or that they that they're
on in the wrong or that they're lying to
you every single day. Right? So, you
just get manipulators and gaslighters
and people that are insane. They tell
you that you're insane because they're
insane, right? because they just want to
want to run away and walk away from
everything that they do and never take
accountability for anything. It's been
like that for 10 years. I have to take
accountability for everything people lie
about my face about,
right? I have to live other people's
lies.
How would you feel about that? How would
you feel about that? You don't think I
want to get vindicated when people keep
lying about me and they're still
actively doing it in order to maintain a
[__] lie because they live in a
satanic cult and I keep saying it every
day and then I wonder where's the police
or FBI or anything cuz I don't want to
live a life like that. I'm a victim of
something that shouldn't be happening
which is called human trafficking,
right? Talk about Epstein. Here's
another thing. They keep doing it. It's
disgusting and it's been 10 years. I
look at it down the [__] throat every
day. You want to talk Epstein
about being called something like that
every [__] day. I don't do nothing.
Look at my [__] life. Right.
It's just [__] annoying.
It's it's beyond annoying because it's
defamation. It's it's it's a ruining a
life, right? You can understand that
America has ruined my life.
It's a systematic thing, right?
You know, I don't trust any
so I don't believe you.
I think everybody's
everybody's a disappointment.
There was a mistake to believe that I
have friends.
Thank you.
Try lighting reality itself
like sensical and well it is nonsensical
but it's because people ruin my life,
you know. It's it's like it's a
reinforcing thing that I think people
should go to jail for because it wasn't
of everyone. They're attempting to human
traffic. They've been doing it openly
for 10 years and more.
And I don't understand why there's no
police or no FBI or no CIA anywhere
inside America that does anything about
anything ever because what's going on is
wrong.
what's going on is too much. I don't
want to be part of it. I don't want to
be stalked. I don't want to be obsessed
about. I don't want to be lied to.
I don't want to have my life changed
around
expressing myself.
So, that's what I'm focusing on now. The
internet.
That's my house.
That's my world. I can't
I can't
I don't have a career. I don't have
anything I can look to and say, "Look, I
have this. People don't No. No. I can't.
No. Don't Don't Don't. No. No. No. I
don't want your advice. No. Just No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. Don't. I I can't
I I'm don't want to. No.
Don't Don't change me. I don't I don't
want advice.
I want this problem fixed.
Yeah, that's fine. But I don't have that
option.
No, I don't.
No, I don't need advice.
I don't need advice.
I need the world to change.
I need the world to listen and act.
I don't I don't need the world's advice.
I'm in the afterlife. I I don't I don't
what what I don't need people's advice.
I just need the world to listen and
change and do what I say.
That's it.
I know it's the world doesn't change for
anybody. It changes for me.
That's fine. Well,
it's not fine. But uh the world changes.
My job is to uh I will subdue these and
uh be the king of uh
you know it will change for me. These
people will change for me. Their souls
will change or or I will I will bind
them to the afterlife.
Will bind them to me.
Yes, I will.
I I don't care what you say my job is,
but that's not my purpose in life. My
purpose is different than that. That's
You're talking about yourself.
No,
no,
no. I I don't like No.
Go [__] yourself.
As I said, I will talk to potatoes
and potatoes alone. I wasted time on
you.
You don't You don't define me. You're a
mud dweller. You don't define me.
You don't define me. You don't give me
advice. You're not my teacher. You're
not my dad. You're nothing to me. You're
not my friend. You're nobody.
So, let's just recalibrate whatever we
learned so far. Cancel all of that.
You're not my friend. You're not potato.
You don't give me advice. I don't want
to listen to you. These things are rude.
I don't need advice from strangers.
There you go. So, you can apologize for
that because I don't need that karma.
You wasted my time.
Your life.
I'm not here to My life is fine.
You know what's not fine is that the
world around me is decaying.
You know that you're the one who should
change. You're the one who should repent
your sins.
You're the one who knows what you're
doing. You're the one who's stalling,
right? You're the one who's avoiding
growth.
Everything you just said, that's what
you should apply to you, right? Go to a
mirror and take all your own advice.
I'm going to time you out for 5 minutes.
You're not my friend. If you want to be
my friend, you grow a potato.
You know, all the nonsense you say. It
makes no sense. I have to delete it
because like
we can't have that standing there,
right? We can't have that. That's You
didn't add anything to the table, then
that's embarrassing. I don't want to
like I don't want to make it seem like
when people come in here that people
don't know how to add something to the
table,
right? If you're going to be potato. I
like potatoes. Potatoes are like, right?
So, you can be a Well, I don't give a
[__] about you.
I don't want your advice. I want you to
change.
It's early morning. It's 6 6:30 in the
morning. Uh, I'm pissed off. Why am I
pissed off? I'm pissed off because
America owes me. I don't own it. I own
their houses. I own their mud back
at least.
And you can't replace that. You can't
give me 10 years of my life back.
Be number one.
You You gave me number last without any
option for anything else.
Well, I don't know why you give energy
to those. You're you're in their
space.
Maybe you should tell people that
they're disgusting for doing that. I
don't know.
Or maybe you shouldn't hang out in their
space. Like, why why are you even in
their space?
Why you even near them? Every time
you're near them, you show them what
they like, you know?
Why don't you call the police?
Or why don't you walk away from them? Or
why
why do you touch them? I don't touch
them. I sacrifice my life to separate
myself from them. You connect me to
them, me and them. Right. You're a
[__] jerk. Not just a jerk, you're an
[__] You're a [__] piece of [__]
Do you not understand that yet?
Like, don't you get it? You're a part of
the satanic cult. I don't want to touch
it. I don't want to touch you.
I don't want to be near these people. If
they're near any of these people,
they're like, if you're near them, if
you're near any of these people, you are
them. You are you are you're satanic
[__] cult, dude.
Open a case.
That's interesting. That's good.
Totally good.
It's just it's messed up. Like, you know
what I'm saying? It's like I like I
can't I don't I I can't I understand
that you're not like them, right? Like I
understand that I'm not AR cuz I don't I
don't I can't I can't control what
people do. I just know that I can't I
I'm just I'm so tired. Good.
You know, I'm angry at them for good
reason.
The latest update is that
yeah, the latest update
is that probably nothing's going to
happen.
You know, it's just you see how America
has no justice system whatsoever. I
don't know why. Why is there even an FBI
and a police and CIA? What do they do?
What does FBI and CIA
do? And the police
like what do they do?
Are they part of it? Like are they part
of the crimes?
Because what? Like it's just I don't
understand
how it can keep going on, you know? It's
like I think I
Yeah,
I think um I reported this like many
years ago. They point out that they were
doing crimes
back in 2018.